"February 14
Wednesday"
Shido! Happy Valentine's!
Yeah. Thanks, Tohka.
Mm-hmm! I'm proud of these!
Can I open it?
Of course you can!
Is it kinako-flavored?
Yup, you know it!
I made 'em with all my heart!
My golden wings shall spread and fly!
Present. We've been waiting
to give these to you.
Thanks. And you even came
all the way to my classroom.
Ooh!
Origami...
Yes?
Uh, how to put it...?
It's incredible. Thank you.
I'm glad.
That's really impressive.
--Damn you! Damn you! Damn you!
--Die! Die! Die!
--Curse you! Curse you! Curse you!
Fellow men, let us commence the ritual!
"Itsuka"
You deserve every ounce of our hatred!
Yes, eat! Feast upon it!
Jeez, they're unbelievable...
Guys, over here!
That's so lame.
--Come get it!
Thank you! Thank you!
Who knew chocolate from a girl
tasted so much sweeter?!
"Giri Choco"
Praise our saviors! Our goddesses!
My, my. You're all so lively this morning.
Good morning, Shido.
Kurumi...
There's no need to be so tense.
Let's save the fun for later, shall we?
Yeah, I can't wait. I've already set up
a room for you in the Spirit dorm.
Oh, my.
Kurumi.
Oh?
What's new with you, Shido?
Not much. Just came to
ask you out on a date.
Oh, my! If you're up for it, I'd love to!
--Shall we?
--Yeah.
Shido... Good luck!
"1. Home"
"2. Karaoke"
"3. Net Café"
Shido, some choices came up.
Let's decide where to go.
Hold up, Kotori.
Huh?
I've already decided where I'll take her.
In other words, you don't
trust my capabilities?
No, it's not like that, MARIA...
Just kidding. We serve as a support role.
If you have a strong conviction,
you should follow it. Right, Commander?
Sure. After all, he's the world's best
specialist at dealing with Spirits.
Go for it.
Thanks, Kotori, MARIA...
Sorry to make you wait.
It's okay. By the way, Shido,
there's somewhere I'd like to go.
I had somewhere in mind, too.
Probably the same place as you.
My, my. Then let's see if you're right.
Lead the way to where
you think I want to go.
Hmm? So this is where
you wanted to bring me?
That's right.
You want to see me in
my underwear that badly?
N-No, that's not it!
Well, I do, but that's beside the point!
--You guessed right.
--Eh?
I wanted to come here, too.
Do you remember bringing
one of my clones to this place?
Ever since, I've always wondered
how the "me" who was with you felt.
What was she thinking--the "me"
whose heart you managed to steal?
Although she was naïve,
she was still "me."
Are you sure you want the same date?
Huh?
Clone or not, I made
Kurumi Tokisaki fall for me.
I'll take you on the same
date as back then.
At the end of today, you won't
be able to think of anything but me.
You really think you can
make me fall for you?
Of course.
Do you remember this place, Shido?
I sure do. This is where you
made me watch you fight Mana.
Oh, I almost forgot...
Happy Valentine's.
Thanks! Did you really forget?
Yeah. It goes to show how much fun I had.
I dare say, it's one of the
best days I can remember.
I've got something, too.
Happy Valentine's, Kurumi.
Oh, my!
There's no rule against
a guy giving out chocolate.
Open it up.
All right. You, too.
Okay.
Are these candied orange peels
in the chocolate? Delicious!
Yours are good, too!
Is this hazelnut I taste?
Not bad, not bad...
"Happiness Meter"
"Mood"
"Mental State"
Kurumi isn't lying--she's genuinely
enjoying today's date.
She hasn't closed her heart off, either.
If anything, she's fond of him.
However, there's something
holding her back:
A resolve, some will, or the like.
Until we root out whatever it is,
we won't be able to seal her power.
A resolve... Some will...
Hey, Kurumi.
Yes, Shido?
Mind telling me why you want
to kill the Spirit of Origin?
You heard it from Nia?
What a blabbermouth.
Shido, are you prepared to know the truth?
About my... everything.
Yeah.
We've lost cameras and intercom.
We're completely cut off from Shido.
Send some replacements!
Shido...
And how about now?
Even now.
This is...?
A nearby abandoned building.
It's one of my bases.
Shido, you said you're prepared to
know everything there is about me.
In that case, please take it all in.
Zaphkiel, Yod.
Kurumi... Kurumi!
Come, I'm right here!
Kurumi!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
It's okay, you're safe now.
Thanks so much!
No more climbing up trees!
That was cool of you, Kurumi.
Thank you, Sawa.
You're like a hero of justice.
You're always helping the elderly
and kids who've lost their way.
That's not--
Their town destroyed by civil war,
20,000 refugees have fled to camps.
"Breaking News"
"Border Conflict Worsens: "It's like hell...'"
"Civil War Displaces 20,000 Refugees"
But in these unsanitary camps,
disease runs rampant.
Kurumi, would you like
to come to my place?
Huh?
I bet Marron would love to see you again.
Remember? The American Shorthair
you played with last time.
Really?! You sure you don't mind?!
Of course not! Marron will love it!
It was so cute!
No!
Huh?
Are you okay?
Th-Thank you.
You saved me. What was that?
A Spirit--monsters which
destroy the world.
Spirit?
Who are you? Why are you here?
Um, my name's Kurumi Tokisaki.
I was just heading home...
And wandered here on your own?
Hmm. Perhaps you have the affinity.
Affinity? Who are you exactly?
I'm Mio Takamiya.
You could say I'm a hero of justice.
Spirits are my enemy.
They're of the same ilk to what attacked
you--monsters which harm the world.
Kurumi, do you wish for power?
Power?
Surely you're compatible with Sephirah.
Join me, and let's save the world.
Save... the world.
Huh?!
I knew I was right about you.
Now, don your Spirit armor.
Huh?
With this, you should instinctively know
your powers and how to use them.
D-Deploy Spirit armor...
Huh?!
This is... me?!
I've long searched for an ally
who could help and fight at my side.
Kurumi Tokisaki, I believe you can.
Help me defeat Spirits and save the world.
Zaphkiel, Het.
Does it make me stand out too much?
Kurumi? Is something wrong?
Sawa! N-No, it's nothing!
Your eye still isn't better?
Y-Yeah, I guess it's one stubborn sty.
That's no good. I hope you get well.
Thank you.
Want to come to my place after school?
My aunt's bringing
Marron's siblings to play.
Really?! Uh...
I-I'm terribly sorry, but I have
plans I can't miss today.
Yeah? That's too bad.
You sure are busy lately.
I'm sorry. But please,
ask me some other time!
Yeah, of course.
For real! I mean it!
A-All right.
Kurumi, I'm counting on you again.
Of course. Leave it to me, Mio.
Deploy Spirit armor, Elohim!
Zaphkiel!
This should do it.
So persistent.
Good work. As always,
I'll take care of the cleanup.
Yes, thank you. Have a good day.
If I hurry, I might be able to visit Sawa.
Wait... What if I invited Mio?
We haven't had many chances to chat...
Mio!
Sawa?!
It's someone you know?
I'm sorry to hear that.
What a shame. I hoped to have
you as a partner for longer.
Spirits are humans
who were given Sephirah.
No, it's more accurate to say
I bestowed them my power.
Z-Zaphkiel, Daletto!
I'm shocked. You avoided
inversion all on your own.
That's a relief. It'd be bothersome if
your refined Sephirah went back to normal.
Inversion? Refined?
Initially, Sephirah aren't
compatible with humans.
Unable to control its power,
they go berserk when given one.
Like this girl whom you killed.
To make Sephirah compatible with humans,
they must be refined.
That is, by giving them
to humans, over and over.
The humans will go berserk, of course,
but in time, the Sephirah
will turn compatible.
Only then will a human with strong
affinity remain themselves as a Spirit.
One like you.
But recovering Sephirah can be difficult.
You've been a great help.
How could you do this?!
I have no grudge against you people.
However, I cannot stop
until I achieve my goal.
Until then, good night, Kurumi.
Kurumi...
The Spirit took away my memories.
The only reason I remember
is thanks to Zaphkiel.
I will kill the Spirit of Origin...
No matter what it takes.
"Episode 11:
'Past Sins.'"
Kurumi Tokisaki: A Spirit crueler
and kinder than anyone.
What is her resolve? What is her will?
Next time: "Cycle of Salvation."
The Worst Spirit shows her devotion.
"Episode 12: 'Cycle of Salvation.'"